socialclicks.com 2015-11-14

# Privacy Policy - AreaOne

AreaOne™ Privacy Policy  
This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) that governs how we, AreaOne Ltd. (“AreaOne”, “we”, “our” or “us”), use Personal Information (defined below) that we collect, receive and store about individuals in connection with the use of: (i) the website www.AreaOne.com (together with its sub-domains, content and services, the “Site”); and (ii) our informative and marketing services (the “Service”). The Site and Service are individually and collectively referred to herein as the “Services”.  
1\. Introduction. We have implemented this Privacy Policy because your privacy, and the privacy of other users of the Services, is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Information is collected and used in connection with the Services. “Personal Information” means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, an email address, a home or other physical address, or other contact information.  
2\. Terms of Service and Service Agreement. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Service, available at http://www.AreaOne.com/terms-of-service/ (“Terms of Service”) and, if applicable, the Service agreement or insertion order that you entered into with AreaOne (“Service Agreement”).  
3\. Consent and Modification. By using the Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to AreaOne’ processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or otherwise use the Services. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such change will be effective ten (10) days following posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site, and your continued use of the Services thereafter means that you accept those changes.  
4\. What Personal Information We Collect and How We Collect It. We receive and/or collect Personal Information from you in the following ways:  
4.1. Site Account. In order to access and use certain parts of the Site and Service, you may be required to access a Site account (“Account”). In order to create an Account you will be asked to provide us with certain Personal Information which may include a company name, company address, contact name, and contact email address, and other designated information.  
4.2. ‘Contact Us’ Information. If you choose to send us a “Contact Us” request, whether by submitting an online form that we make available on the Site, or by sending an email to an email address that we display on the Site, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information such as your name. You may also choose to provide us with your phone number and email address as well as any other information that you submit.  
4.3. Log Files. The Site may make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, clicked pages and any other information your browser may send to us. We may use such information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user’s movement around the Site, and gather demographic information.  
4.4. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. Our Services may utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Certain cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information, such as an IP address, previously indicated by a Services user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.  
4.5. Opt-Out. At any time you may Opt-Out of AreaOne’s services.  
You are free to delete all cookies on your browser, either delete all cookies or specifically AreaOne.com cookies, or to have your browser notify you when a cookie is set – simply check your browser settings to do so. By deleting your cookies in this manner you will disable AreaOne and its Partners to deliver ads that are targeted to your interests. You will have to clear your cookies each time you visit AreaOne.com or one of our Advertiser’s websites to ensure you are not receiving retargeted advertisements.  
4.6. Mobile Opt Out  
How to opt out of interest based advertising on iOS and Android based devices:  
iOS Device  
iOS 7 or Higher  
Go to your Settings > Select Privacy > Select Advertising > Enable the “Limit Ad Tracking” setting  
iOS 6  
Go to your Settings >Select General > Select About > Select Advertising > Enable the “Limit Ads Tracking” setting  
More information about the iOS setting can be found here.  
Android Device  
For Android devices with OS 2.2 and up and Google Play Services version 4.0 and up:  
Open your Google Settings app > Ads > Enable “Opt out of interest-based advertising”  
If you’ve turned on Limit Ad Tracking on your iOS device or the Opt out of interest-based ads on your Android device, you can restore interest-based ads by turning the settings off.  
4.7. Personal Information. AreaOne does not sell, trade, rent, or release your personal information to third parties in ways that are not disclosed in the privacy statement.  
5\. Ads. As part of the Service we may place advertisements on a third party website or service (each an “Ad”), such as Facebook™. We do not use Personal Information to determine the placement of Ads. Rather, our placement of Ads is based on general criteria, keywords and topics (for example, individuals aged between 18-35 years of age, people who like the keyword “music”, or people who are interested in football). We may utilize cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present Ads, and to help measure and research the Ads’ effectiveness. We do not collect Personal Information from Ads. We may collect aggregate and anonymous information from Ads which does not directly enable identification of an individual and cannot reasonably be used to identify an individual (“Anonymous Information”).  
6\. The Way We Use Personal Information. If you submit or we collect Personal Information through the Services, then such Personal Information may be used in the following ways:  
6.1. We will use your Personal Information to provide and improve our Services, to contact you in connection with the Services and certain programs or offerings that you may have registered for, and to identify and authenticate your access to the parts of the Services that you are authorized to access.  
6.2. We may use your designated email address and contact information to: (i) send you updates or news regarding the Services including our products and services; and/or (ii) respond to a “Contact Us” or administrative request (for example in connection with your Account).  
6.3. We may share your Personal Information with our subsidiaries or affiliated companies for the purpose of storing or processing such information on our behalf. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy.  
6.4. We may share your Personal Information with our third party service providers (such as a hosting provider or a payment processor), but only to assist us with our business operations and to provide our Services. Such information may be transferred to other countries around the world. We use commercially reasonable efforts to only engage or interact with third party service providers that post a privacy policy governing their processing of Personal Information.  
6.5. We may disclose your Personal Information or any information you submitted via the Services if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; (ii) enforce our Terms of Service and/or Service Agreement, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; or (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of AreaOne, its users, yourself or the public.  
7\. Use of Anonymous Information. We may use Anonymous Information or share it with our customers and third party service providers in order to provide and improve our Services. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and partners.  
8\. Opting Out. You may choose not to receive future promotional, advertising, or other emails related to the Services from us by selecting an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email that you receive from us. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving the foregoing emails, we may still send you a response to any “Contact Us” request as well as administrative emails (for example, in connection with your Account) that are necessary to facilitate your use of the Services.  
9\. Choice. At all times, you may choose whether or not to provide or disclose Personal Information. The notices that we provide on the Site in circumstances where we collect Personal Information should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you may still visit and access parts of the Services, but you may be unable to visit or access certain options, programs, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.  
10\. Access/Accuracy. To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, AreaOne wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. We may provide Site tools which enable you to remove or modify certain information from or in your Account. If you would like to delete or correct any other of your Personal Information that we may be storing, you may submit a request to us by sending an email to info@AreaOne.com. Your email should include adequate details of your request.  
11\. Links to Other Sites. The Site may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by AreaOne. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party websites.  
12\. Children’s Privacy. The Services are not structured to attract children under the age of 13 years. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at info@AreaOne.com.  
13\. Security. The security of Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards, including the use of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards, to protect the Personal Information that we collect or that is submitted to us. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security or confidentiality. If you have any questions about security on the Services, you can contact us at info@AreaOne.com.  
14\. Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy. In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, or in the event of bankruptcy or a comparable event, we reserve the right to transfer or assign Personal Information in connection with the foregoing events.  
15\. California Privacy Rights. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of AreaOne who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to info@AreaOne.com. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year.  
16\. Commitment. We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and we are constantly evolving our Services to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or your Personal Information that we may be storing and using, please contact us at info@AreaOne.com.  
Last updated: 27 November 2014
